[

](https://goosevpn.com/)×

* 
* 
* 

**Your IP**

**ISP**

**Location**

[

](https://goosevpn.com/)[BUY NOW](https://my.goosevpn.com/sign-up) [Log in](https://my.goosevpn.com/login)

English

4.1

* Products

###### MOBILE

* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-iphone)[IOS](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-iphone)
* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-android)[ANDROID](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-android)

###### DESKTOP

* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-mac)[MACOS](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-mac)
* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-windows)[WINDOWS](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-windows)
* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/linux-vpn)[LINUX](https://goosevpn.com/linux-vpn)

###### OTHER

* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-routers)[ROUTERS](https://goosevpn.com/vpn-routers)
* [
    
    ](https://goosevpn.com/android-tv-vpn)[ANDROID TV](https://goosevpn.com/android-tv-vpn)

GOOSE VPN Privacy Policy
========================

By using the GOOSE VPN service you agree to our [Terms of Service](https://goosevpn.com/terms-of-service), [Privacy Policy](https://goosevpn.com/privacy-policy) and [Refund Policy](https://goosevpn.com/refund-policy).

Services Goose BV.
------------------

The service GOOSE VPN provided by Goose BV. (referred to hereafter as: “Goose”) concerns the security and protection of data sent via the internet and allows users to browse the internet unrestricted. Goose owns and administers the website, goosevpn.com, and all the information that is collected on the website, advertises for the services of Goose, maintains the Goose CMS-system, processes payments and administers refunds for the services of Goose that have been purchased through the website goosevpn.com and offers pre-sales and aftersales support to all customers of Goose. We consider the protection of your personal information extremely important. In this privacy policy, you can read how we handle your personal data: (I) general, (II) when you visit our website; and (III) when you use GOOSE VPN.

**I. General**
--------------

The term personal data encompasses all information about an identifiable, natural person, including, but not limited to, first and last name, house- and work address, credit card data, e-mail address and other contact details. For the sake of this privacy policy, we will consider IP-addresses (internet-protocol) personal identifiable information as well.

Legal basis for the use of personal data

Goose processes your personal data exclusively on the basis of the legal grounds referred to hereafter as intended in article 6 of the General Data Protection Regulation:

* Creating/executing an agreement with the person concerned
* Permission of the person concerned – Please note: you can withdraw this permission at any time
* Legal requirements that Goose is obliged to follow
* Justified (commercial) interest of Goose

**Security Measures**

Goose ensures that – taking the level of the technology into account – appropriate technical and organizational security measures are taken to guarantee a level of security appropriate to the risks.

**Disclosing of personal data to third parties**

Goose does not sell, rent or trade your personal data to third parties. Goose shares your personal data only insofar as it is necessary for providing the services while taking the purposes mentioned above into account. If Goose employs the services of a party who processes your personal data in Goose’s name and at Goose’s behest, a processor’s agreement will be made with that party.

**Retention Policy**

Your personal data will not be stored any longer than is necessary for the purposes described in this privacy policy.

**Your privacy rights**

You have numerous privacy rights. A request to insight, correction, limitation, protest and transferal of data, removal of your personal data or withdrawal of permission granted earlier can all be made via our contact form. Within 4 weeks of receiving your request, you will receive word from us. We may ask you – to be certain that you were the one to file the request – to send a copy of your ID along as well. In this copy, blacken out your passport photograph, MRZ, passport number and social security number. If you are displeased with our treatment of your personal data, you can file a complaint with the Data Protection Authority.

**II. Privacy on the website goosevpn.com**
-------------------------------------------

**Processing personal data – website**

Should you be visiting our website, Goose processes your personal data in the following cases:

* Access – you have access to content on the website goosevpn.com without registering and without providing any personal identifiable information;
* Contact – When you contact our online helpdesk, the helpdesk employee will be able to see your country of origin and the local IP-address. This data will not be stored. You are not required to provide our helpdesk employee your name, e-mail address or other personal information. When you contact our helpdesk by e-mail, we will store your e-mail address.
* Surveys – We do not collect any of our personal data when you fill out an online survey.

Goose does not intend to process personal data or processing data on visitors to the website that are younger than 16 years of age. For this reason, Goose requests that this data not be sent.

**Use of your personal data – website**

Your personal data can be used for the following purposes:

* Chat-helpdesk: through personal data that you have provided us when using the online chat-helpdesk, we can send answers directly to your e-mail address, should the chat-session be interrupted. We do not add your e-mail address to our mailing list automatically.
* Mail-helpdesk: through personal data that you have provided us when contacting our e-mail helpdesk, we can send the answers to your questions directly to your e-mail address. We do not add your e-mail address to our mailing list automatically.
* Mailings: Should you give us permission to, Goose can, using the e-mail address you have provided, keep you informed of the most recent service information, software-updates, offers and promotions and improve our service, website and advertising campaigns. If you do not wish to remain part of our mailing list, you can unsubscribe while subscribing or do so later, by unsubscribing using the footer in one of our e-mails.

**Cookies and other technologies – website**

The website, e-mails and advertisements of Goose may employ the use of ‘cookies’ and other technologies such as pixeltags and web beacons. Using these technologies, Goose can gain better insight into user behavior, knowledge of which parts of our website have been visited and the effectivity of advertisements and internet searches can be facilitated and measured. All information that is collected with cookies and other technologies, is stored and treated as personally non-identifiable data. Goose also makes use of cookies and other technologies to store information when you visit our website. Our goal in these instances is the improvement of your experience with Goose. Should you wish to deactivate cookies, go to the security settings of your browser and turn cookies off. On a mobile device, go to the section marked cookies at settings or preferences. With specific browsers, contact your provider on how to disable cookies. Keep in mind that certain functions of Goose’s website are not available when cookies are turned off. In certain e-mails, we make use of a ‘click-through URL’, that refers you to content on the website goosevpn.com. When customers click on a URL such as this, it is possible that they are first routed through a separate GOOSE-webserver before they reach designated page. We collect this clickthrough-data to ascertain the interest in certain subjects as well as the effectiveness of our customer communication. If you would rather that this clickthrough data is not collected in this manner, do not click on textual or graphic links in e-mail messages. Pixeltags allow us to send e-mails in a format that is legible to our customers. We can use this information to limit or eliminate messages for our customers.

**Security Measures – Website**

The online cash registers, my account-pages and the helpdesk portal of Goose use SSL-encryption (Secure Sockets Layer) on all webpages where personal data is collected. To make use of an SSL-encryption of personal data that is transferred through the internet to these pages, you will have to use an SSL-browser. When you use Goose’s online chat-helpdesk, the personal information that you share will be visible to the helpdesk employee and can be read and/or used by him/her. You yourself are responsible for the personal data (such as your name and e-mail address) that you provide in such instances.

**III. Privacy on GOOSE VPN’s secure VPN server network**
---------------------------------------------------------

Using Goose’s services encompasses the sending of data through the internet via servers and IP-addresses from the server network of Goose by means of the VPN software application: GOOSE VPN. The server network of Goose is property of and is administrated and monitored by Goose BV in Rotterdam, the Netherlands. GOOSE VPN is developed, maintained and administrated by Goose BV in Rotterdam, the Netherlands.

**Processing personal data – VPN-services**

When you use GOOSE VPN, Goose processes personal data in the following instances:

* When you register for a free trial or a paid service of GOOSE VPN, we save the e-mail address that you provide us. This data, combined with your account data as a user of GOOSE VPN, is stored in our CMS-system on one of our secure servers;
* We do not register your IP-address when you sign up or log into your GOOSE account.
* When you sign up, we register your IP-address one time only;
* When you use GOOSE VPN, Goose collects information on the actual bandwidth consumption per user account.
* Payment details? –
* When logging onto the website, Goose stores the last-used IP-address. However, this does not apply to the application or other actions, Goose does not save the IP-address (internet protocol) in a cache memory, nor does it collect or save this;
* Goose does not save any data concerning the servers or the IP-address on the server network of Goose when a user is connected on a certain time or in general, in a cache memory nor does it collect it or store it;
* Goose does not save any registrations of internet activities of users (for example, websites visited, DNS-search results, e-mails sent and received, usernames or entered passwords, etc.) in a cache memory nor does it collect this, or save this, or aggregates this, or use this through the network servers of GOOSE VPN.

**Use of personal data – VPN-services**

Your personal data can be used for the following purposes:

* The e-mail address that you provide us when you sign up for a free trial or a paid service of GOOSE VPN is used to send you the data pertaining to your user account. The e-mail address that you provide us can also be used to send you important notifications such as communication about purchases or changes to our terms of use and policy. Because this information is important to you as a user of GOOSE VPN, you will not be able to unsubscribe from these mailings.
* Goose does not censor nor monitor the internet activity of users;
* Goose does not censor nor monitor or creates back-ups of users’ e-mails

**Cookies and other technologies – VPN-services**

Goose does not use any cookies or other technologies on the servers of Goose. Not a single outgoing server of the server network of Goose contains information on the server, on the network or of users. The operating system of the servers is turned off except for modules that are necessary for the transferal of internet traffic.

**Security Measures – VPN-services**

All servers of Goose are secured with Linux hardening, firewalls and software is installed against spam, viruses and DDOS-attacks to prevent third-parties from carrying out malicious attacks on the server network of Goose. We maintain our servers and networks to offer as much privacy as possible. Goose does its utmost to protect information about bandwidth use of users and all related data from loss, theft or unauthorized access, abuse, disclosure, alteration and destruction. This includes, but is not limited to, the beneficial application of bandwidth use of users between the server network of Goose and the network maintenance system of Goose.

**Questions about privacy**

Should you have questions or comments on Goose’s privacy policy, please contact us through the contact form. GOOSE VPN can actualize the privacy policy at set times. If we thoroughly adjust the policy, a message will be placed on our website along with the updates to our privacy policy.

**Cookies and other technologies – website**

**Necessary cookies**

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name** | **Placed by** | **Expires after** | **What purpose** |
| lang\_switch | GOOSE VPN | 1 year | Stores the language of the user to show the correct website |
| lang\_switchToENG | GOOSE VPN | 1 year | Saves language of choice |
| \_hjIncludedInSample | GOOSE VPN | 1 year | Maintains users’ statuses on page visits |
| \_\_cfduid | GOOSE VPN | 1 year | Used by the content network, Cloudflare, to identify trusted web traffic |
| show\_not | GOOSE VPN | 1 year | Used to save the first visit |

**Analytical cookies**

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name** | **Placed by** | **Expires after** | **What purpose** |
| \_ga | Google Analytics | 2 years | Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website |
| \_gid | Google Analytics | End of session | Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical dats on how the visitor uses the website |
| \_gat | Google Analytics | End of session | Used by Google Analytics to slow down request speed |

**Marketing cookies**

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name** | **Placed by** | **Expires after** | **What purpose** |
| ACT | Facebook | End of session | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| C\_USER | Facebook | 6 months | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| DATR | Facebook | 2 years | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| FR  | Facebook | 6 months | Measures conversions and provides targeted offers on sites of third parties. The used conversion information is anonymous. |
| PL  | Facebook | 6 months | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| PRESENCE | Facebook | End of session | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| SB  | Facebook | 2 years | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| WD  | Facebook | 1 week | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| XS  | Facebook | 6 months | Should a visitor be logged onto Facebook, Facebook can store cookies on his/her computer that are necessary to like messages and to update his/her status |
| 1P\_JAR | Google | 1 month | These cookies are used by Google to show adjusted advertisements on Google-sites, based on recent searches and other interactions |
| AID | Google | 1,5 years | These cookies link your activities on other devices that you have logged onto earlier with your Google account. |
| APISID | Google | 2 years | These cookies are used by Google to show adjusted advertisements on Google-sites, based on recent searches and other interactions |
| HSID | Google | 2 years | Ensures that Google can collect user information for video’s hosted by Youtube. |
| NID | Google | 6 months | These cookies are used by Google to show adjusted advertisements on Google-sites, based on recent searches and other interactions |
| OGPC | Google | 3 months | Google places a cookie to measure clicks and requests to optimize our advertisement campaigns |
| S   | Google | End of session |     |
| SAPISID | Google | 2 years | Ensures that Google can collect user information for video’s hosted by Youtube. |
| SID | Google | 2 years | These cookies are used by Google to show adjusted advertisements on Google-sites, based on recent searches and other interactions |
| SIDCC | Google | 6 months | Cookie placed by Youtube to create a link to various Google services |
| SSID | Google | 2 years | Ensures that Google can collect user information for video’s hosted by Youtube. |
| OTZ | Google | 1 year | Is used by Google Analytics to keep track of website visits |
| UULE | Google | 1 day | Is used by Google Analytics to keep track of website visits |
| AID | Google | 1,5 years | Helps advertisers to determine how many people that clicked their advertisement convert. |
| \_utma | FMTC | 2 years | Collects data on the number of times that a user has visited the website, as well as data for the first and most recent visit. Used by Google Analytics. |
| \_utmb | FMTC | 1 hour | Registers a timestamp with the exact point in time that the user visited the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the length of a stay on a website. |
| \_utmc | FMTC | End of session | Registers a timestamp with the exact point in time that the user left the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the length of a stay on a website. |
| \_utmt | FMTC | 10 minutes | Is used to manage the speed of requests to the server. |
| \_utmv | FMTC | End of session | Is used for analytical purposes. |
| \_utmz | FMTC | 6 months | Collects data on where the user came from, what search engine was used, what link was clicked and what search term was used. Used by Google Analytics. |
| APISID | Youtube | 2 years | Cookie that provides insight into which media used by Google Adwords is effective. |
| HSID | Youtube | 2 years | Cookie that provides insight into which media used by Google Adwords is effective. |
| PREF | Youtube | 6 months | An enclosed Youtube-video collects visitor information and adjusted preference settings. |
| SAPISID | Youtube | 2 years | Cookie that provides insight into which media used by Google Adwords is effective. |
| SID | Youtube | 2 years | Protects user data from unauthorized access |
| SSID | Youtube | 2 years | Cookie that provides insight into which media used by Google Adwords is effective. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_Live | Youtube | 6 months | Attempts to estimate the bandwidth of users on pages with integrated Youtube-videos. |
| YSC | Youtube | End of session | An enclosed Youtube-video collects visitor information and adjusted preference settings. |
| GPS | Youtube | End of session | Registers a unique ID on mobile devices that makes tracking possible based on geographical GPS-location. |
| \_livechat | Livechatinc.com | 3 years | Is used to hide the personal adjustment of the user to LiveChat |
| \_livechat\_lastvisit | Livechatinc.com | 3 years | Registers when the user used LiveChat last |
| 3rdparty | Livechatinc.com |     | Is used to hide the personal adjustment of the user to LiveChat |
| PAPCookie\_Imp\_\* | Postaffiliatepro.com |     | Is used to track referrals |
| PAPVisitorId | Postaffiliatepro.com |     | Is used to save the visitor’s ID for tracking referrals |
| TP.uuid | Trustpilot.com | 20 years |     |
| \_auc | Trustpilot.com | 16 months |     |
| \_zlcmid | Trustpilot.com | 1 year |     |
| amplitude\_id\_\* | Trustpilot.com | 1 year |     |
| \_zlcprivacy | Trustpilot.com | 2 years |     |
|     |     |     |     |

[Home](https://goosevpn.com/) » Privacy Policy

[

](https://goosevpn.com/)

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Name** | GOOSE B.V. |
| **Address** | Treubstraat 31 |
|     | 2288EH Rijswijk |
|     | The Netherlands |
| **Chamber of Commerce** | 34278975 |
| **VAT** | NL818275066B01 |
| **Email** | [\[email protected\]](https://goosevpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) |

Please note: we do not provide telephone support but are available 24/7 by email.

#### About us

#### Apps

#### Support

#### VPN Benefits

* 

* 

* 

* 

© 2024 GOOSEVPN. All rights reserved.

[Home](https://goosevpn.com/) » Privacy Policy

#### About us

#### Apps

#### Support

[

](https://goosevpn.com/)

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Name** | GOOSE B.V. |
| **Address** | Treubstraat 31 |
|     | 2288EH Rijswijk |
|     | The Netherlands |
| **Chamber of Commerce** | 34278975 |
| **VAT** | NL818275066B01 |
| **Email** | [\[email protected\]](https://goosevpn.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) |

Please note: we do not provide telephone support but are available 24/7 by email.

* 

* 

* 

* 

© 2024 GOOSEVPN. All rights reserved.

Close this module

Choose for lifetime privacyGet 50% discount on our Lifetime VPN! 🧡

Pay only once and take advantage of the best deal and be assured of secure and borderless internet for a lifetime!
